Menu

Privacy Policy of Steganos Software GmbH
----------------------------------------

The Steganos company slogan "Privacy made easy" makes it clear that our customers' need for privacy is our focus. The protection of personal data is therefore of the highest priority for us - compliance with the legal provisions on data protection is a matter of course for us.

In the following we would like to briefly explain how Steganos stands on data protection, how exactly we protect your data and what it means for you when you use our personalizable services.

### Personal Information

Personal data is the data that can be used to determine your identity. These can be: Name, address, postal address and telephone number. Information that is not directly associated with your real identity, such as favourite websites or the number of users of a website, is not included here.

The content of our website can be used without revealing your identity. If you register for one of our personalized services, order a product or subscribe, we will ask you for your email address and other personal information. It is your free decision whether you enter this data. However, should you decide to purchase one of our software products, you will be asked for certain personal data that are necessary to complete the purchase process. This data depends on the payment model you have chosen. The data will only be used by the partners responsible at the time of the order to process the purchase process and will only be stored for this purpose. These data - unless absolutely necessary for the execution of the purchase process - will not be made accessible to third parties in extracts.

If you contact our customer service via the contact form, your request will be stored in a database together with the information voluntarily provided therein (if available). This information is used exclusively by our customer service to process your request. The data collected in this way is also used for statistical evaluations within Steganos Software GmbH. Neither the raw data nor the results of the evaluations will be made available to third parties, even in part.

We store your data on specially protected Steganos servers in Germany. Access to it is only possible for a few specially authorised persons. All identity-related information is only collected by us if you have expressly permitted us to do so.

### Disclosure of personal information to third parties

Steganos does not pass on personal user data to third parties unless the user has given his express prior consent or there is a legal obligation to do so. An exception are certain technical service providers carefully selected by us and bound by our instructions who take on certain tasks for us. These tasks include, for example, sending our newsletter (order data processing) or collecting and processing anonymous data on user behavior or collecting information on software errors that have occurred in order to improve the Steganos website.

### Right of revocation

If you have provided us with personal data, you can have it deleted at any time. Data for accounting and bookkeeping purposes are not necessarily affected by a cancellation or deletion.

### Use of cookies

Cookies are small files that can be "set" by a server (e.g. the servers of the Steganos Online Shield website) on a user's computer. These files may contain various information, including personal information such as personal settings, in order to improve the use of an Internet offer. The Steganos Online Shield website uses cookies to record session information, e.g. to adapt the display of web pages to the user profile. Most browsers are set to automatically accept cookies. Every user can configure his browser in such a way that all or certain cookies are accepted or rejected or that a request for permission is made before a cookie is set. How this works can be found in the documentation of the respective browser or in its "help".

In some areas of our website, we use cookies to implement user functions that would otherwise not be usable.

The use of our generally accessible offers is also possible without cookies.

### Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. "("Google") Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties if this is required by law or if third parties process this data on behalf of Google. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

### Children

Persons under the age of 18 should not transmit any personal data to us without the consent of their parents or legal guardians.

### Amendment of the Directives

Steganos reserves the right to change the data protection guidelines at any time in compliance with data protection regulations.

### Your rights, questions and comments

If you need information about the data stored by us or have questions, suggestions or comments concerning the protection of your data, please send us an e-mail to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it..

* You are here:  
* Privacy Policy 

HOME

PRODUCTS

SERVICE

NEWSLETTER

Subscribe to our newsletter here. By doing so, you consent to the processing of your data in accordance with our [Privacy Policy](https://www.steganos.com/en/privacy-policy). You can unsubscribe at any time.

PRODUCT RECOMMENDATIONS
